[
  {
    "question": "The SI unit of pressure is ______.",
    "options": ["Pascal", "Bar", "atm", "Newton"],
    "answer": "Pascal"
  },
  {
    "question": "The boiling point of water on the Kelvin scale is ______.",
    "options": ["273 K", "0 K", "373 K", "100 K"],
    "answer": "373 K"
  },
  {
    "question": "The process in which a solid directly changes into gas without becoming liquid is called ______.",
    "options": ["Evaporation", "Condensation", "Sublimation", "Melting"],
    "answer": "Sublimation"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Boyle’s Law, the product of pressure and volume at constant temperature is a ______.",
    "options": ["Zero", "Constant", "Variable", "Negative value"],
    "answer": "Constant"
  },
  {
    "question": "______ thermometer is used to measure human body temperature.",
    "options": ["Laboratory", "Clinical", "Digital", "Room"],
    "answer": "Clinical"
  },
  {
    "question": "Plasma state contains ______ particles.",
    "options": ["Neutral", "Solid", "Ionized", "Compressed"],
    "answer": "Ionized"
  },
  {
    "question": "During melting, the temperature of the substance remains ______.",
    "options": ["Decreasing", "Constant", "Increasing", "Unstable"],
    "answer": "Constant"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mercury is used in thermometers because it expands ______ with temperature.",
    "options": ["Linearly", "Randomly", "Slowly", "Irregularly"],
    "answer": "Linearly"
  },
  {
    "question": "The specific heat capacity of water is ______ J/kg°C.",
    "options": ["100", "1", "4186", "273"],
    "answer": "4186"
  },
  {
    "question": "Charles’s Law relates volume and ______ at constant pressure.",
    "options": ["Mass", "Temperature", "Density", "Area"],
    "answer": "Temperature"
  }
]
